Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy. UARC.0401
UCLA Library Special Collections
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy.
1935-1971
UCLA Library Special Collections
University of California, Los Angeles. Office of the Chancellor
UARC.0401
53.7 Linear Feet (134 boxes)
Record Series 401 contains the administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy from the period of time during which Murphy served as UCLA Chancellor. Materials in this record series date from 1935-1971 and include correspondence, memorandum, and reports on all aspects of UCLA university business as it relates to the campus, to the University of California system, to Los Angeles and Southern California, and to UCLA's emergence as a major U.S. research university.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934669903606533
Biographical History
Franklin D. Murphy served as UCLA's third Chancellor from 1960-1968. Murphy's two predecessors were:
Raymond B. Allen, 1952-1958
Vern O. Knudsen, 1959-1960
In 1969 Charles E. Young succeeded Murphy as UCLA Chancellor.
Prior to the 1952 creation of UCLA's Office of the Chancellor, there was a series of chief administrative officers and titles for the Los Angeles campus including: Director; Vice-President and Director; and Vice-President and Provost.
Franklin David Murphy was born in Kansas City, MO, January 29, 1916; AB University of Kansas (1936); MD University of Pennsylvania (1941). Murphy served as an instructor (1946-1948) and Dean (1948-1951) of the University of Kansas School of Medicine. From 1951-1960 Murphy served as Chancellor of the University of Kansas.
Scope and Content
Record Series 401 contains the administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy from the period of time during which Murphy served as UCLA Chancellor. Materials in this record series date from 1935-1971 and include correspondence, memorandum, and reports on all aspects of UCLA university business as it relates to the campus, to the University of California system, to Los Angeles and Southern California, and to UCLA's emergence as a major U.S. research university.
Chancellor's Communications Service (CCS) staff organized, described, and indexed the Office of the Chancellor's files for day-to-day use; file names located in the 'Container List' include the file index codes assigned by the CCS.
Franklin D. Murphy chancellorial files not transferred to the UCLA University Archives include materials relating to legal actions and materials subject to state/federal privacy regulations.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
Related Materials
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files, 1936-1959 (University Archives Record Series 359). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, University Archives, University of California, Los Angeles.
Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young, 1965-1997 (University Archives Record Series 583). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, University Archives, University of California, Los Angeles.
Franklin D. Murphy papers (LSC 363). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
"My UCLA chancellorship oral history transcript: an utterly candid view." Franklin D. Murphy [oral history transcript 300/122]. UCLA Library Special Collections, Center for Oral History Research interview, date of interview. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
- Directives (Chancellor)., 1969 Feb-1970 Jun. (Box 1)
  General note
  Index code 1-Dir.
- Directives (President)., 1958-1964. (Box 1)
- Directives (President)., 1965-1967. (Box 2)
- Directives (President)., 1968-1969 Apr. (Box 3)
- Directives (President)., 1969 Apr-1970 Aug. (Box 4)
- Academic Plan for Los Angeles., 1958; 1961-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 5)
  Index code 1.
- Agriculture, College of., 1960-1965. (Box 5)
  Index code 1-Agric.
- Agriculture, College of. Transfer from UCLA to Riverside., 1958-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 5)
- Architecture and Urban Planning, School of., 1965-1969. (Box 5)
  Index code 1-Arch.
- Architecture and Urban Planning, School of. Establishment of., 1958-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 5)
- Directives (President)., 1970 Sep. (Box 5)
- Schools and Colleges, General., 1960-1970. (Box 5)
- Statewide Academic Plan., 1958-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 5)
- Business Administration, School of. California Management Review., 1957-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 6)
  Index code 1-BusAd.
- Business Administration, School of. Phasing out of Undergraduate School of Business Administration., 1962-1965. (Box 6)
  Scope and Contents note
- Business Administration, Graduate School of. UCLA Business Research Associates., 1957-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 6)
  Index code 1-GradBus.
- Business Adminstration, School of., 1960-1968; 1970. (Box 6)
  Index code 1-BusAd
- Graduate School of Business Administration. (IBM 709). Western Data Processing Center., 1959-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 6)
  Index code 1-GradBusAd.
- Dentistry, School of., 1960-1970. (Box 7)
  Index code 1-Dent.
- Education, School of., 1958-1970. (Box 7)
  Index code 1-Educ.
- Education, School of. Crawford/Keislar Suit., 1961-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 7)
- Graduate School of Business Administration. Western Management Science., 1959-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 7)
- Education, School of. High School Teachers Awards., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 8)
- Engineering, College of., 1959-1969. (Box 8)
  Index code 1-Engin.
- Engineering, College of. Reorganization and Change from College to a School., 1966-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 8)
- Engineering, School of. Academic Plan for Engineering., 1960-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 8)
- Engineering, School of. Engineering Curriculum Study (Ford Foundation)., 1956-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 8)
- Engineering, School of. Engineering Enrollment., 1946-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 8)
- Fine Arts, College of., 1960-1965. (Box 9)
  Index code 1-FA.
- Fine Arts, College of. Establishment of the College., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 9)
- Letters and Science, College of., 1959-1969. (Box 9)
  Index code 1-L&S
- Library Science, School of., 1960-1968. (Box 9)
  Index code 1-Lib.
- Library Science, School of. Establishment of., 1953-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 9)
- Medicine, School of., 1965-1970. (Box 9)
  Index code 1-Med.
- Medicine, School of. 10-Year Plan for the Health Sciences (CEY's Membership on Committee)., 1970. (Box 10)
- Medicine, School of. Compensation Plan (Private Practice Plan) for Clinical Faculty Members., 1953-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 10)
- Medicine, School of. Comprehensive 10-Year Plan for the Health Sciences., 1968-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 10)
- Medicine, School of. Health Sciences Facilities. West Medical Campus. E. Todd Wheeler. Consultant., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 10)
- Medicine, School of. Health Sciences Planning Goals (Dentistry, Medicine, Nursing, Public Health)., 1964-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 10)
- Medicine, School of. Interns and Residents (House Staff)., 1961-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 11)
- Medicine, School of. Minority Students. Discrimination/Recruitment in School of Medicine., 1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 11)
- Medicine, School of. Regional Medical Program., 1967-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 11)
- Medicine, School of. Report of Medical Education Costs to CCHE by President's Advisory Committee., 1960-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 11)
- Nursing, School of., 1960-1964; 1967-1970. (Box 11)
  Index code 1-Nurs.
- Occupational and Vocational Courses., 1957-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 12)
  Index code 1-Occ.
- Occupational and Vocational Courses. Applied Arts., 1957-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 12)
- Occupational and Vocational Courses. Business Education., 1957-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 12)
- Occupational and Vocational Courses. Social Welfare., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 12)
- Occupational and Vocational Courses. Vocational Education., 1956-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 12)
- Public Health, School of., 1960-1961; 1963-1970. (Box 12)
  Index code 1-PubHlth.
- Air Science, Department of., 1960-1961. (Box 13)
  Index code 2-AirSci.
- Anatomy, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 13)
  Index code 2-Ana.
- Anthropology-Sociology, Department of., 1960-1969. (Box 13)
  Index code 2-Anth.
- Art, Department of., 1959-1970. (Box 13)
  Index code 2-Art.
- Art, Department of. Henri Matissa Art Collection., 1964-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 13)
- Art, Department of. Leonardo da Vinci Festival., 1962-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 13)
- Art, Department of. Occupational and Vocational Courses., 1958-1959. (Box 13)
- Astronomy, Department of., 1959-1970. (Box 13)
  Index code 2-Astron.
- Departments, General., 1960-1970. (Box 13)
  Index code 2.
- Social Welfare, School of., 1961-1970. (Box 13)
  Index code 1-SocWelf.
- Biomathematics, Department of., 1967. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Biomath.
- Biophysics and Nuclear Medicine, Department of., 1960-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Biophys.
- Botany, Department of., 1962-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Bot.
- Chemistry, Department of., 1960-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Chem.
- Classics, Department of., 1960-1966. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Class.
- Dance, Department of., 1965-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Dance.
- Economics, Department of., 1960-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Econ.
- English, Department of., 1961-1970. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Engl.
- French, Department of., 1963-1964. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Fren.
- Geography, Department of., 1962-1963. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Geog.
- Geology, Department of., 1962-1969. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Geol.
- History, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Hist.
- Home Economics, Department of. Occupational and Vocational Courses., 1957-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Home.
- Italian, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Ital.
- Journalism, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 14)
  Index code 2-Journ.
- Journalism, Department of. Foreign Press Awards., 1960-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 14)
- Linguistics, Department of., 1965-1970. (Box 15)
  Index code 2-Ling.
- Linguistics, Department of. Establishment of Department of Linguistics., 1965-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 15)
- Mathematics, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 15)
  Index code 2-Math.
- Medical Departments., 1960-1969. (Box 15)
  Index code 2-Med.
- Meteorology, Department of., 1963; 1965-1969. (Box 15)
  Index code 2-Meteor.
- Military Science, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 15)
  Index code 2-Mili.
- Military Science, Department of. Commission on ROTC., 1969-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 15)
- Military Science, Department of. Compulsory ROTC., 1958-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 16)
  Index code 2-MiliSci.
- Music, Department of. Ethnomusicology., 1960-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 16)
  Index code 2-Music.
- Music, Department of. University Band Trip to Europe., 1959-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 16)
- Music, Departmet of., 1960-1969. (Box 16)
- Near Eastern Languages, Department of., 1961-1969. (Box 16)
  Index code 2-NE.
- Opthalmology, Department of., 1968. (Box 16)
  Index code 2-Opthal.
- Oriental Languages, Department of., 1963; 1967-1968. (Box 16)
  Index code 2-Orien.
- Pathology, Department of., 1961. (Box 16)
  Index code 2-Path.
- Reports., 1965-1970. (Box 16)
  Index code 16-Rpts.
- Philosophy, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Phil.
- Physical Education, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-PE.
- Physical Education, Department of. Occupational and Vocational Courses., 1957-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 17)
- Physics, Departmet of., 1960-1964. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Phyc.
- Planetary and Space Physics, Department of., 1965-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Planet.
- Political Science, Department of., 1960-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-PoliSci.
- Psychology Clinic School, 1959-1967. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-PsychClin.
- Psychology, Department of., 1963; 1965-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Psych.
- Radiology, Department of., 1958-1965. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Radiol.
- Radiology, Department of. Proposed Private Practice Plan for Radiologists., 1952-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 17)
- Sociology, Department of., 1965-1970. (Box 17)
  Index code 2-Sociol.
- Speech, Department of., 1963; 1967-1970. (Box 18)
  Index code 2-Speech.
- Subject A, Department of., 1960-1965. (Box 18)
  Index code 2-SubA.
- Teacher Training, 1962-1966. (Box 18)
  Index code 2-TT.
- Theatre Arts - Occupational and Vocational Courses, 1958-1960. (Box 18)
  Index code 2-TA.
- Theatre Arts, Department of., 1958-1962; 1965-1970. (Box 18)
- Zoology, Department of., 1961-1964. (Box 18)
  Index code 2-Zoo.
- Academic Communications Facility, 1961-1970. (Box 19)
  Index code 3.
- Academic Senate. General Matters., 1960-1970. (Box 20)
  Index code 5.
- Academic Senate. Statewide., 1964. (Box 20)
- Budget and Interdepartmental Relations, Committee on., 1961-1970. (Box 20)
  Index code 5-Bud.
- Courses and Curriculum, 1960-1970. (Box 20)
  Index code 4.
- Educational Policy Commitee., 1960-1967. (Box 20)
  Index code 5-E.
- UCLA-Irvine/Academic Communications Facility., 1968-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 20)
- Academic Personnel Matters., 1960-1961. (Box 21)
  Index code 9.
- All University Conference., 1960-1969. (Box 21)
  Index code 6.
- Faculty Clubs (Men and Women)., 1960-1969. (Box 21)
  Index code 8.
- Graduate Division. Academic Senate. Graduate Council Statewide., 1961-1969. (Box 21)
  Index code 5-Grad.
- Leaves., 1960-1969. (Box 21)
  Index code 7.
- Research Committee. L.A. Division., 1950-1970. (Box 21)
  Index code 5-Res.
- Sabbatical Leave Policy., 1946-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 21)
- Academic Personnel Matters, 1962-1968. (Box 22)
- Academic Personnel Matters., 1969 Jan-Jul, 1969 Oct-Dec. (Box 23)
- Administrative Stipends., 1959-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 23)
- Directors. Appointments and Review. Use of Title. Senate Memberships., 1953-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 23)
- Faculty Effort and Output., 1968-1969. (Box 23)
- Faculty Workloads., 1935-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 23)
- Recruitment., 1960-1964. (Box 23)
- Academic Personnel. General., 1969-1970. (Box 24)
  Index code 9.1.
- Academic Personnel. General., 1969-1970. (Box 24)
- Faculty Summer Fellowships., 1961-1968. (Box 24)
  Index code 9-F.
- General. FTE., 1969-1970. (Box 24)
- Regents' Professorships and Lectureships., 1959-1963. (Box 24)
- Salaries (Merit Increases, Overscale, etc.), 1960-1962. (Box 24)
  Index code 9-S.
- Academic Freedom., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.11.
- Decentralization and Administrative Organization., 1960-1965. (Box 25)
  Index code 10.
- Faculty Effort and Output. Workload., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.7.
- Individual Biography, Bibliography, Honors., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.8.
- Leaves, Sabbaticals, and Vacations. Policy and Routine., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.3.
- Policy and COC, 1969-1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.4.
- Salaries., 1963. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.5.
- Tenure Faculty. Appointment and Promotion., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.6.
- Titles., 1970. (Box 25)
  Index code 9.2.
- Decentralization and Administrative Organization., 1966-1970. (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Admission. Relations with School and College. Placement., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Environmental Health and Safety., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Gifts and Endowments., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Non-Academic Personnel Program., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Police., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Publications., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Purchasing., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization of Statewide Institutes., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization Questionnaire., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Decentralization. General., 1959-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 26)
- Faculty Participation in Governance., 1970. (Box 26)
  Index code 10.5.
- Honors to Faculty and Staff., 1964-1970. (Box 26)
  Index code 11.
- Athletic Contracts and Agreements., 1960-1970. (Box 27)
  Index code 14-C-A.
- Athletics Department., 1965-1970. (Box 27)
  Index code 14.
- Honors to Students., 1965-1969. (Box 27)
  Index code 12.
- IAAC (Intercollegiate Athletic Advisory Committee), 1960-1968. (Box 27)
- Intercollegiate Athletics, Department of., 1960-1964. (Box 27)
- NCAA (National Collegiate Athletics Association)., 1960-1970. (Box 27)
- Peace Corps., 1965-1970. (Box 27)
  Index code 13.
- Rose Bowl., 1961-1966. (Box 27)
- Senate Committee on Athletics., 1960-1961. (Box 27)
- Tickets and Ticket Office., 1961-1970. (Box 27)
- Athletic Association of Western Universities., 1960-1964. (Box 28)
  Index code 14-AAWU.
- Chancellor's Athletic Advisory Committee., 1968. (Box 28)
  Index code 14-CAAC.
- Chancellor's Intercollegiate Athletic Advisory Board. Minutes of Meetings., 1960-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 28)
- Crew., 1961-1967. (Box 28)
  Index code 14-Crew.
- Academic Salaries., 1965-1968. (Box 29)
  Index code 15-Ac.
- Athletic Association of Western Universities., 1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 29)
- PAC 8, 1965-1970.; 1 bound volume (Box 29)
- Academic Salaries., 1969-1970. (Box 30)
- Accounting Office., 1960. (Box 30)
  Index code 16.
- Administrative Salaries., 1963-1969. (Box 30)
  Index code 15-Adm.
- Cashier., 1961-1962. (Box 30)
  Index code 15-Cash.
- Non-Academic Salaries., 1965-1970. (Box 30)
  Index code 15-NA.
- Salaries. Booz, Allen, and Hamilton., 1968-1970. (Box 30)
  Index code 15-Sal.
- Accounting Office., 1961-1968; 1970. (Box 31)
- Admissions., 1960-1970. (Box 32)
  Index code 17.
- Architects and Engineers, Decentralization of., 1960-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 32)
  Index code 18.
- Architects and Engineers., 1960-1970. (Box 32)
- Bel-Air Property (9.27 Acres)., 1958-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 32)
  Index code 18P.
- Budget Matters., 1960; 1963-1964. (Box 32)
  Index code 19.
- Campus Planning Committee., 1960-1969. (Box 32)
- Closing of Westwood Boulevard., 1958-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 32)
- 1960-1961 Budget., 1959-1960. (Box 33)
  Index code 19-60-61.
- 1961-1962 Budget., 1960. (Box 33)
  Index code 19-61-62.
- 1962-1963 Budget. (Box 33)
  Index code 19-62-63.
- Budget Matters., 1965-1970. (Box 33)
- Business Office., 1960-1964; 1967-1970. (Box 33)
  Index code 20.
- Business Office. MR&A., 1964; 1969; 1970. (Box 33)
- Central Garage., 1960-1964; 1967-1696. (Box 34)
  Index code 21.
- Central Stage Management., 1963-1696. (Box 34)
  Index code 23.
- Identification Cards., 1962-1969. (Box 34)
- UCLA Guest House., 1961-1965. (Box 34)
  Index code 24.
- University Elementary School., 1967-1970. (Box 34)
  Index code 22.
- Graduate Division., 1960-1970. (Box 35)
  Index code 25.
- Graduate Fellowships., 1960-1964. (Box 35)
  Index code 25-GF.
- Dean of Students (General)., 1960-1969. (Box 36)
  Index code 26.
- Educational Opportunities Program., 1963-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 36)
- Foreign Students., 1960-1964. (Box 36)
  Index code 26-FS.
- International Student Center., 1955-1962. (Box 36)
- University Sponsorship of Non-Citizens., 1954-1964. (Box 36)
- National Defense Education Act of 1958., 1958-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 37)
  Index code 26-P&S.
- NDEA. Disclaimer., 1951-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 37)
- Prizes and Scholarships., 1959-1964. (Box 37)
- Student Loan Funds., 1960-1964. (Box 37)
  Index code 26-L.
- Western Area Council on International Students (UCLA)., 1952-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 37)
- NDEA. Title II. Student Loans., 1958-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 38)
- NDEA. Title IV. National Defense Act., 1964-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 38)
- NDEA. Title IV. National Defense Graduate Fellowships., 1958-1963.; 2 bound volumes (Box 38)
- NDEA. Title V. Guidance, Counseling, and Testing., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 38)
- NDEA. Title V-B. Counseling and Guidance Training Institute., 1958-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 38)
- NDEA. Title VI. Language Development Program., 1958-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 38)
- NDEA. Section 1001 (d)., 1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 39)
- NDEA. Title VII. Research and Experimentation in More Effective Utilization of Media for Education., 1958-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 39)
- NDEA. Title X. Improvement of Statistical Services of State Educational Agencies., 1958-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 39)
- Non-Academic Personnel Matters., 1960-1963. (Box 39)
  Index code 28.
- Relations with Schools., 1960-1969. (Box 39)
  Index code 27.
- Advisory Committee on Equal Opportunity and Fair Treatment., 1964-1965. (Box 41)
- Non-Academic Personnel Matters., 1964-1970. (Box 41)
- Staff Personnel Matters. Affirmative Action Program., 1970. (Box 41)
- Authority to Appoint Administrative Officers. Decentralization of Non-Academic Personnel Functions., 1959.; 1 bound volume (Box 42)
  Index code 28-Pers.
- Fair Employment Practices Commission., 1963-1970. (Box 42)
  Index code 28-FEPC.
- Grievances and Appeals., 1964-1969. (Box 42)
  Index code 28-GR&A.
- Hospital Staff Personnel., 1966-1970. (Box 42)
  Index code 28-Hospital.
- Operating Engineers' Strike., 1969. (Box 42)
- Overtime Payments to Non-Academic Employees., 1954-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 42)
- Title and Code Changes., 1963-1970. (Box 42)
  Index code 28-T&C.
- University Policies Governing Relationships with Employee Organizations., 1962-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 42)
- Wage Scales and Union Matters., 1960-1970. (Box 42)
  Index code 28-W.
- International Medical Programs. Spallino v. Tugazy., 1962-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 43)
  Index code 29.
- Medical Programs Abroad., 1964-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 43)
- University Extension., 1960-1970. (Box 43)
- Buildings and Grounds, Department of., 1961; 1963-1969. (Box 44)
  Index code 30.
- Committee on Fine Arts Production., 1966-1970. (Box 44)
  Index code 29-CTEE.
- Conference and Special Activities, Department of., 1963-1970. (Box 44)
  Index code 29-C.
- Housing Office., 1960-1964. (Box 44)
  Index code 31.
- Barrington Plaza., 1964-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 45)
  Index code 31-Bar.
- Housing Office., 1964-1965; 1967-1969. (Box 45)
- Married Student Housing., 1964-1969.; 1 bound volume (Box 45)
  Index code 31-MSH.
- Married Student Housing., 1957-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 45)
- Library., 1960-1963. (Box 46)
  Index code 33.
- Married Student Housing (Sepulveda Park and Park Vista)., 1964-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 46)
- Park Vista Apartments/Sepulveda Park Apartments., 1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 46)
- Residence Halls., 1965-1970. (Box 46)
  Index code 31-Res.
- Biomedical Library., 1960-1969. (Box 47)
  Index code 33-B.
- Law School Library., 1961-1962. (Box 47)
  Index code 33-L.
- Librarian's Association. Use of University Name., 1967-1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 47)
- Library., 1963-1970. (Box 47)
- William Andrew Clark Memorial Library., 1960-1970. (Box 47)
  Index code 33-C.
- Administrative Commitees (President's)., 1969-1970. (Box 48)
  Index code 37.
- Committee on Calendar. Proposed New Calendar., 1952-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 48)
  Index code 37-C.
- Mailing Division., 1964-1970. (Box 48)
  Index code 34.
- Police Matters., 1957-1962; 1964-1970. (Box 48)
  Index code 35.
- Administrative Committees., 1963-1970. (Box 49)
  Index code 38.
- Chancellor's Administrative Committees., 1960-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 49)
- Chancellor's Administrative Committees., 1962-1966. (Box 50)
- Audio Visual Instruction, Committee on., 1961. (Box 51)
  Index code 38-Aud.
- Chancellor's Administrative Committees., 1966-1970. (Box 51)
- Chancellor's Building Committees., 1956-1957.; 1 bound volume (Box 51)
  Index code 38-Bldg.
- Administrative Manual., 1955-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 52)
  Index code 39.